

PROFILE

Caring and compassionate man with over one years of experience in web developing.
Passionate about working with various age groups and deeply committed to enhancing and supporting comprehensive work.
Dedicated to clear and thorough communication with clients and support staff.

CONTACT

PHONE: 01778540880

EMAIL

mekail15-13818@diu.edu.bd

ADDRESS:

604/1, Middle Monipur, Mirpur-2, Dhaka-1216

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Surfing Scuba diving Reading Novels Travel Teaching Watching Movies Coding

REFERENCE

Kaium Bin Abu Bakar Additional Secretary Ministry Of Foreign Affairs Phone: 01689447252

MEKAIL TUSHAR

Computer Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Home Tutor

Mirpur, Dhaka

2020- Present

Collaborated with students to complete homework assignments, identify lagging skills and correct weaknesses.

Web Developer

Index It Limited

2021-Present

Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot and other editing software. Applied latest emerging technology, software and project application trends to update and maintain site applicability.

Junior Web Developer CodersTrust Bangladesh

2020-2021

Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.

EDUCATION

2020-Present B.S.E Daffodil International University Subject:

Computer Science and Engineering.

2016-2018 H.S.C St. Joseph Higher Secondary School

Group: Science Result: 5.00

2010-2015 S.S.C Monipur Uccha Biddalaya And College Group:

Science Result: 5.00

KEY SKILLS AND CHARACTERISTICS

- Software Best Practices
- Technical Analysis
- Website optimization
- Web development projects
- Agile Workflow